<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<source>
<publisher>Midland Jobs</publisher>
<publisherurl>https://midlandjobs.ie</publisherurl>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 17:18:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<job>
		<title>Assistant Project Coordinator</title>
		<date>2024-01-12T07:35:44.000000Z</date>
		<expirationdate>2024-03-12T00:00:00.000000Z</expirationdate>
		<referencenumber>2832</referencenumber>
		<url>https://midlandjobs.ie/job/2832/assistant-project-coordinator/</url>
		<city>Mullingar</city>
		<state>County Westmeath</state>
		<country>Ireland</country>
		<postalcode></postalcode>
		<location></location>
		<remote>no</remote>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;IDASO is currently recruiting for a Assistant Project Coordinator role for an immediate start in the midlands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IDASO (Innovative Data Solutions) specialises in providing traffic, transport and mobility data. We offer our data collections services and software solutions to clients worldwide from Maynooth to Malaysia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This role combines the functions of project oversight and client liaison with cost estimation for tender submissions. Oversight of  proven project management workflow ensuring that gating issues are identified in advance and addressed and that the client is informed of progress through the project lifecycle. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interpret client requirements and complete pricing matrix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce professional proposal with accurate costings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete the required documentation and ensure submission within the required timescales.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversight of the project lifecycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify gating issues and potential handover challenges between departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure understanding of client requirements by key team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep client informed of progress through the project lifecycle. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining excellent internal relationships, understanding who to go to in order to gather relevant information and ensuring that good relations are kept with key individuals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Essential&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To be approachable, flexible and adaptable at all times.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a commercial administrative role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication with both verbal and written professional report writing experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can demonstrate Team Work &amp;amp; Collaboration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Microsoft Office Suite, Internet and e-Learning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deadline driven, self-motivated attitude with a focus on seeing tasks through.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Desirable&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project management experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience in preparing and submitting commercial tenders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep relationship building, account management and consultative selling skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of bringing deals to a close and building the pipeline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Results-focused with the ability to deliver on targets and sales goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong influencing skills, with experience coordinating local and remote teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong team player with excellent interpersonal and cross-cultural skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solution-driven problem solver with an innovative approach&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A “can-do” and agile mindset where you thrive in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
					<salary></salary>
			<salaryfrom></salaryfrom>
			<salaryto></salaryto>
			<salaryperiod>yearly</salaryperiod>
				<applyurl>https://midlandjobs.ie/job/2832/assistant-project-coordinator/</applyurl>
		<jobtype>Full time</jobtype>
		<category>Business Development, Consultant, Data Analysis, Engineering, General Business, Project Management</category>
		<company>IDASO Ltd</company>
		<companydescription>&lt;p&gt;IDASO specialises in providing traffic, transport and mobility data for use in Strategic Planning, Traffic Impact Assessments, Property Management and Retail Assessments, along with optimisation of existing transport management systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based in the centre of Ireland at the National Science Park, IDASO offers services and software solutions to clients worldwide from Maynooth to Malaysia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IDASO is a data collection company who use the latest technologies to gather information on traffic patterns to be used by transport planners, consulting engineers and local authorities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/h4srPwCmxk0&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</companydescription>
		<companywebsite>www.idaso.ie</companywebsite>
		<companylogo>https://midlandjobs.ie/files/pictures/Idaso_Logo_2.jpg</companylogo>
			</job>
</source>