<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<source>
<publisher>Midland Jobs</publisher>
<publisherurl>https://midlandjobs.ie</publisherurl>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 16:04:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<job>
		<title>Swimming Pool Manager</title>
		<date>2024-01-10T14:15:36.000000Z</date>
		<expirationdate>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000000Z</expirationdate>
		<referencenumber>2826</referencenumber>
		<url>https://midlandjobs.ie/job/2826/swimming-pool-manager/</url>
		<city>Ballymahon</city>
		<state>County Longford</state>
		<country>Ireland</country>
		<postalcode></postalcode>
		<location></location>
		<remote>no</remote>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re a thriving team passionate about working together to deliver excellence, all in a natural forest environment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in hundreds of acres of beautiful forest Longford Forest is the perfect place for a short break in Ireland, 365 days a year. With homely accommodation, up to 100 indoor and outdoor activities and a choice of bars and restaurants, there is something for all the family, all year round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SWIMMING POOL MANAGER | Circa €53,700 per annum plus 12% bonus scheme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a focal point for every Center Parcs village, our Subtropical Swimming Paradise (STSP) is a real favourite with all our guests and that theme is set to continue here at Longford – in fact, ours is one of a kind and the largest pool in Ireland.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has something for everyone – from whirlpools to cold water plunge pools – and as  Subtropical Swimming Paradise Manager, your role will focus on helping ensure all guests receive a warm welcome, enjoy great times and create unforgettable moments in a safe and superb setting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the Leisure Services Manager, you’ll lead a large and diverse team, with responsibility for the commercial management and day to day operation of all Subtropical Swimming Paradise facilities. This will involve monitoring KPI’s and managing financial budgets, as well as overseeing compliance with all quality and safety requirements, in addition to developing an on-going activity programme and maximising all revenue generating opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT YOU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an Operational Manager you will have strong people management skills as well as technical and commercial know how and direct experience of managing a large/diverse team, ideally in a leisure environment, is essential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As this role forms part of the Center Parcs Longford Forest Management team you should be accustomed to working collaboratively with other functions and key stakeholders to achieve excellent outcomes. We’ll also expect you to display a strong customer focus and good level of financial awareness, including a proven track record in controlling, implementing and managing budgets and driving high service standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desirable Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of swimming pool operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leisure Management Qualification (QQI Level 6)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IWS/National Pool Lifeguard Qualification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pool Plant Operative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Due to the sensitive nature of this role the successful applicant will be required to apply for Garda Vetting. This disclosure, together with other selection information, will need to be satisfactory to the Company for employment to commence.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOURS OF WORK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be contracted to work 160 hours per 4-week period on a flexible basis. This means that your days and hours of work could vary each week but you will always receive your contracted hours per period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your working hours will include days, evenings, weekends, public / bank holidays and during Christmas and/or New Year on a rota basis, with a premium rate of pay for hours worked on a Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE BENEFITS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Center Parcs is a fantastic place to work and the benefits are as impressive as they are unique. Here are just a few:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management Bonus Scheme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pension Scheme with Life Assurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Recognition and Reward Scheme – offering a choice of Center Parcs and High Street vouchers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free use of our leisure facilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discounted Center Parcs breaks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20% discount in our restaurant and retail outlets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to Perks at Work Portal - offering a wide range of retail and leisure discounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Employee Assistance Program - providing support on financial, health and legal matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent opportunities for career development and progression with the opportunity to gain externally recognised qualifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like your ideal job, then we’d love to see your application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
					<salary>€53,700 yearly</salary>
			<salaryfrom>53700</salaryfrom>
			<salaryto>53700</salaryto>
			<salaryperiod>yearly</salaryperiod>
				<applyurl>https://bit.ly/47sfUsK</applyurl>
		<jobtype>Full time</jobtype>
		<category>Leisure</category>
		<company>Center Parcs Ltd</company>
		<companydescription>&lt;p&gt;Imagine being greeted by playful squirrels and a good morning &amp;lsquo;quack!&amp;rsquo; by the local ducks on your commute into work. Imagine having a workplace that&amp;rsquo;s up to 400 acres of beautiful forest. Imagine being part of a family where you love coming to work and helping to make special memories. At Center Parcs, you can have all that and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Housekeeper, Chef, Lifeguard or Electrician, everyone is part of the same Center Parcs family, and no two days are the same. If you are looking for a unique place to work with endless opportunities and famously good staff perks, visit our vacancies page and apply to work at Center Parcs.&lt;/p&gt;</companydescription>
		<companywebsite>https://www.centerparcs.ie/</companywebsite>
		<companylogo>https://midlandjobs.ie/files/pictures/CP_Logo_MASTER_IRELAND_1042x1042_png.png</companylogo>
			</job>
	<job>
		<title>Deputy Restaurant Manager</title>
		<date>2024-01-10T14:14:07.000000Z</date>
		<expirationdate>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000000Z</expirationdate>
		<referencenumber>2825</referencenumber>
		<url>https://midlandjobs.ie/job/2825/deputy-restaurant-manager/</url>
		<city>Ballymahon</city>
		<state>County Longford</state>
		<country>Ireland</country>
		<postalcode></postalcode>
		<location></location>
		<remote>no</remote>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Set in hundreds of acres of beautiful forest Longford Forest is the perfect place for a short break in Ireland, 365 days a year. With homely accommodation, up to 100 indoor and outdoor activities and a choice of bars and restaurants, there is something for all the family, all year round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pancake House&lt;/strong&gt; – The Pancake House is an all-time guest favourite. This popular restaurant serves savoury and sweet pancakes cooked in traditional Dutch style on a griddle, as well as freshly cooked omelettes and waffles. Set in a beautiful location overlooking the lake, The Pancake House is a fabulous family venue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEPUTY RESTAURANT MANAGER | Circa €35,500 per annum&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;All colleagues working in our restaurants, cafés and bars will benefit from the discretionary service charge we add to bills. The majority of our guests are happy to reward our colleagues for their excellent service.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We now have an exciting opportunity for experienced people Manager to join our growing family. We are looking for individuals with leadership, drive and a commitment to deliver consistently great service. In this role, you will assist the Restaurant Manager in effectively controlling, co-ordinating and planning the unit activities in line with Company standards. You will maintain high levels of guest satisfaction through service and value for money to achieve budgeted financial targets. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT YOU&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Deputy Restaurant Manager, you will help lead, motivate and develop the team. This is a hands-on Management role, where you will play an integral part in the day-to-day running of the operation, including taking orders, serving food and ensuring the team deliver excellent service to every guest. Ideally, you will have previous experience as a Deputy Manager/Assistant Manager within a food and beverage environment. You will be a highly motivated individual, committed to the success of the operation. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOURS OF WORK&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be contracted to work 150 hours per 4-week period on a flexible basis. This means that your days and hours of work could vary each week, but you will always receive at least your contracted hours each period. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As our village is open 365 days of the year, your working hours will include weekends, public / bank holidays and during Christmas and / or New Year on a rota basis. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EXPERIENCE, SKILLS &amp;amp; QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to lead a team &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good financial awareness – stocktaking/rotas/analysis &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good level of computer literacy and analytical skills &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Catering/Bar Management experience in a high-volume restaurant/bar environment at Deputy Manager level or as Manager in a smaller unit &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desirable requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Back of House experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Center Parcs is a fantastic place to work and the benefits are as impressive as they are unique. Here are just a few:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Bonus Scheme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pension Scheme with Life Assurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Recognition and Reward Scheme – offering a choice of Center Parcs and High Street vouchers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free use of our leisure facilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discounted Center Parcs breaks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20% discount in our restaurant and retail outlets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to Perks at Work Portal - offering a wide range of retail and leisure discounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Employee Assistance Program - providing support on financial, health and legal matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent opportunities for career development and progression with the opportunity to gain externally recognised qualifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like your ideal job, then we’d love to see your application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
					<salary>€35,500 yearly</salary>
			<salaryfrom>35500</salaryfrom>
			<salaryto>35500</salaryto>
			<salaryperiod>yearly</salaryperiod>
				<applyurl>https://bit.ly/3vqCQvg</applyurl>
		<jobtype>Full time</jobtype>
		<category>Restaurant-Food Service</category>
		<company>Center Parcs Ltd</company>
		<companydescription>&lt;p&gt;Imagine being greeted by playful squirrels and a good morning &amp;lsquo;quack!&amp;rsquo; by the local ducks on your commute into work. Imagine having a workplace that&amp;rsquo;s up to 400 acres of beautiful forest. Imagine being part of a family where you love coming to work and helping to make special memories. At Center Parcs, you can have all that and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Housekeeper, Chef, Lifeguard or Electrician, everyone is part of the same Center Parcs family, and no two days are the same. If you are looking for a unique place to work with endless opportunities and famously good staff perks, visit our vacancies page and apply to work at Center Parcs.&lt;/p&gt;</companydescription>
		<companywebsite>https://www.centerparcs.ie/</companywebsite>
		<companylogo>https://midlandjobs.ie/files/pictures/CP_Logo_MASTER_IRELAND_1042x1042_png.png</companylogo>
			</job>
	<job>
		<title>Linen and Logistics Assistant</title>
		<date>2024-01-10T14:12:23.000000Z</date>
		<expirationdate>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000000Z</expirationdate>
		<referencenumber>2824</referencenumber>
		<url>https://midlandjobs.ie/job/2824/linen-and-logistics-assistant/</url>
		<city>Ballymahon</city>
		<state>County Longford</state>
		<country>Ireland</country>
		<postalcode></postalcode>
		<location></location>
		<remote>no</remote>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re a thriving team passionate about working together to deliver excellence, all in a natural forest environment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in hundreds of acres of beautiful forest Longford Forest is the perfect place for a short break in Ireland, 365 days a year. With homely accommodation, up to 100 indoor and outdoor activities and a choice of bars and restaurants, there is something for all the family, all year round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LINEN AND LOGISTICS ASSISTANT | €12.90 per hour&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Center Parcs all our accommodation has been designed and built to the highest standards, so we need a team to uphold these standards and exceed guest expectation. Our Housekeeping accommodation cleaning team is responsible for maintaining more than 460 Lodges and is the largest team on the village.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an enthusiastic team player to join our busy team as a Linen and Logistics Assistant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this role, you will assist the Accommodation and Housekeeping Services team in the delivery, collection and maintenance of furniture, inventory and linen items to guest accommodation and other areas across the village in a timely and efficient manner. You will also be responsible for supporting linen, logistics and central inventory stores in receiving deliveries, managing stock and storage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will have excellent communication skills, an eye for detail and a willingness to learn. You will also have excellent customer service skills and be willing to work outside in all weathers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that this role involves heavy physical work activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOURS OF WORK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be contracted to work 38 hours per 4-week period. Your hours of work will be working on a Monday and Friday from 10:00am to 2:45pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be required to work some public/bank holidays on a rota basis. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EXPERIENCE, SKILLS &amp;amp; QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An awareness of general standards of cleanliness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full driving licence held for a minimum of 6 months (ability to drive a van)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desirable requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience within a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE BENEFITS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Center Parcs is a fantastic place to work and the benefits are as impressive as they are unique. Here are just a few:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Bonus Scheme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pension Scheme with Life Assurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Recognition and Reward Scheme – offering a choice of Center Parcs and High Street vouchers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free use of our leisure facilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discounted Center Parcs breaks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20% discount in our restaurant and retail outlets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Employee Assistance Program - providing support on financial, health and legal matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent opportunities for career development and progression with the opportunity to gain externally recognised qualifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like your ideal job, then we’d love to see your application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
					<salary>€12.90 hourly</salary>
			<salaryfrom>12.90</salaryfrom>
			<salaryto>12.90</salaryto>
			<salaryperiod>hourly</salaryperiod>
				<applyurl>https://bit.ly/3vuY62Z</applyurl>
		<jobtype>Part time</jobtype>
		<category>Hospitality-Hotel</category>
		<company>Center Parcs Ltd</company>
		<companydescription>&lt;p&gt;Imagine being greeted by playful squirrels and a good morning &amp;lsquo;quack!&amp;rsquo; by the local ducks on your commute into work. Imagine having a workplace that&amp;rsquo;s up to 400 acres of beautiful forest. Imagine being part of a family where you love coming to work and helping to make special memories. At Center Parcs, you can have all that and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Housekeeper, Chef, Lifeguard or Electrician, everyone is part of the same Center Parcs family, and no two days are the same. If you are looking for a unique place to work with endless opportunities and famously good staff perks, visit our vacancies page and apply to work at Center Parcs.&lt;/p&gt;</companydescription>
		<companywebsite>https://www.centerparcs.ie/</companywebsite>
		<companylogo>https://midlandjobs.ie/files/pictures/CP_Logo_MASTER_IRELAND_1042x1042_png.png</companylogo>
			</job>
	<job>
		<title>Housekeeping Team Leader - Accommodation</title>
		<date>2024-01-10T14:11:19.000000Z</date>
		<expirationdate>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000000Z</expirationdate>
		<referencenumber>2823</referencenumber>
		<url>https://midlandjobs.ie/job/2823/housekeeping-team-leader-accommodation/</url>
		<city>Ballymahon</city>
		<state>County Longford</state>
		<country>Ireland</country>
		<postalcode></postalcode>
		<location></location>
		<remote>no</remote>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re a thriving team passionate about working together to deliver excellence, all in a natural forest environment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in hundreds of acres of beautiful forest Longford Forest is the perfect place for a short break in Ireland, 365 days a year. With homely accommodation, up to 100 indoor and outdoor activities and a choice of bars and restaurants, there is something for all the family, all year round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOUSEKEEPING TEAM LEADER – ACCOMODATION | €15.19 Per Hour&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this role you will have responsibility for supervising one of the teams of Housekeeping Assistants, within the Accommodation division, ensuring the smooth and efficient running of the cleaning operation. You will provide training and development to your team to ensure the highest standards of cleanliness and hygiene are achieved on a daily basis. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Team Leader, you will assist with the organisation and allocation of duties, motivate, develop and coach your team, monitor cleaning standards and ensure maximum security is maintained within the housekeeping department in relation to keys, stores, guests and company property at all times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The role will be very ‘hands on’, leading from the front, working with your team to ensure all guests receive an amazing Center Parcs experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT YOU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good verbal and written communication skills are required, along with an organised and methodical approach to work.  The ideal candidate will be flexible and adaptable, have a motivational approach and have previous supervisory experience. Previous experience within the cleaning / hospitality industry would be preferred but not essential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOURS OF WORK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be contracted to work 64 hours per 4-week period on a flexible basis, which means your days and hours of work could vary each week but you will always receive your contracted hours each period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will also be required to work weekends and public/bank holidays on a rota basis with a premium rate of pay for hours worked on a Sunday. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE BENEFITS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Center Parcs is a fantastic place to work and the benefits are as impressive as they are unique. Here are just a few:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Bonus Scheme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pension Scheme with Life Assurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Recognition and Reward Scheme – offering a choice of Center Parcs and High Street vouchers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free use of our leisure facilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discounted Center Parcs breaks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20% discount in our restaurant and retail outlets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Employee Assistance Program - providing support on financial, health and legal matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent opportunities for career development and progression with the opportunity to gain externally recognised qualifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like your ideal job, then we’d love to see your application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
					<salary>€15.19 hourly</salary>
			<salaryfrom>15.19</salaryfrom>
			<salaryto>15.19</salaryto>
			<salaryperiod>hourly</salaryperiod>
				<applyurl>https://bit.ly/41T8kpJ</applyurl>
		<jobtype>Part time</jobtype>
		<category>Hospitality-Hotel</category>
		<company>Center Parcs Ltd</company>
		<companydescription>&lt;p&gt;Imagine being greeted by playful squirrels and a good morning &amp;lsquo;quack!&amp;rsquo; by the local ducks on your commute into work. Imagine having a workplace that&amp;rsquo;s up to 400 acres of beautiful forest. Imagine being part of a family where you love coming to work and helping to make special memories. At Center Parcs, you can have all that and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Housekeeper, Chef, Lifeguard or Electrician, everyone is part of the same Center Parcs family, and no two days are the same. If you are looking for a unique place to work with endless opportunities and famously good staff perks, visit our vacancies page and apply to work at Center Parcs.&lt;/p&gt;</companydescription>
		<companywebsite>https://www.centerparcs.ie/</companywebsite>
		<companylogo>https://midlandjobs.ie/files/pictures/CP_Logo_MASTER_IRELAND_1042x1042_png.png</companylogo>
			</job>
	<job>
		<title>Maintenance Technician - Painter / Decorator</title>
		<date>2024-01-10T14:09:56.000000Z</date>
		<expirationdate>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000000Z</expirationdate>
		<referencenumber>2822</referencenumber>
		<url>https://midlandjobs.ie/job/2822/maintenance-technician-painter-decorator/</url>
		<city>Ballymahon</city>
		<state>County Longford</state>
		<country>Ireland</country>
		<postalcode></postalcode>
		<location></location>
		<remote>no</remote>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re a thriving team passionate about working together to deliver excellence, all in a natural forest environment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in hundreds of acres of beautiful forest Longford Forest is the perfect place for a short break in Ireland, 365 days a year. With homely accommodation, up to 100 indoor and outdoor activities and a choice of bars and restaurants, there is something for all the family, all year round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MAINTENANCE TECHNICIAN - PAINTER / DECORATOR | €14.19 per hour&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have an exciting opportunity to join our Maintenance team at Longford Forest as Maintenance Technician – Painter/Decorator&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your responsibilities will be:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To undertake planned works, working to an agreed programme, within accommodation units on changeover days and central building facilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completing reactive work orders in the allotted time scale for each set of works&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working within and as part of the Technical Services Maintenance Team and proactively identifying and consulting on task trends and recurring issues which may cause future maintenance problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with and fully coordinating works with the Accommodation Services teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT YOU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Essential requirements:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A full current full Irish/EU, Class B (+E), Drivers Licence as you will be required to drive work vehicles around site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NFQ Level 6 Advanced Certificate Craft – Painting and Decorating, demonstrable equivalent (i.e. National Craft Certificate) or a minimum of 2 years’ relevant trade experience working with a Painting Contractor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to execute work without supervision and with attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work effectively and as part of a team in dynamic and high pressure situations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOURS OF WORK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be contracted to work 150 hours per 4-week period on a flexible basis.  This means that your days and hours of work may vary but you will always receive at least your contracted hours each period. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your working hours will include some weekends, public/bank holidays and during Christmas and/or New Year on a rota basis, with a premium rate of pay for hours worked on a Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE BENEFITS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Center Parcs is a fantastic place to work and the benefits are as impressive as they are unique. Here are just a few:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Bonus Scheme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pension Scheme with Life Assurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Recognition and Reward Scheme – offering a choice of Center Parcs and High Street vouchers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free use of our leisure facilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discounted Center Parcs breaks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20% discount in our restaurant and retail outlets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to Perks at Work Portal - offering a wide range of retail and leisure discounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Employee Assistance Program - providing support on financial, health and legal matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent opportunities for career development and progression with the opportunity to gain externally recognised qualifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like your ideal job, then we’d love to see your application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
					<salary>€14.19 hourly</salary>
			<salaryfrom>14.19</salaryfrom>
			<salaryto>14.19</salaryto>
			<salaryperiod>hourly</salaryperiod>
				<applyurl>https://bit.ly/3vA39Po</applyurl>
		<jobtype>Full time</jobtype>
		<category>Skilled Labor</category>
		<company>Center Parcs Ltd</company>
		<companydescription>&lt;p&gt;Imagine being greeted by playful squirrels and a good morning &amp;lsquo;quack!&amp;rsquo; by the local ducks on your commute into work. Imagine having a workplace that&amp;rsquo;s up to 400 acres of beautiful forest. Imagine being part of a family where you love coming to work and helping to make special memories. At Center Parcs, you can have all that and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Housekeeper, Chef, Lifeguard or Electrician, everyone is part of the same Center Parcs family, and no two days are the same. If you are looking for a unique place to work with endless opportunities and famously good staff perks, visit our vacancies page and apply to work at Center Parcs.&lt;/p&gt;</companydescription>
		<companywebsite>https://www.centerparcs.ie/</companywebsite>
		<companylogo>https://midlandjobs.ie/files/pictures/CP_Logo_MASTER_IRELAND_1042x1042_png.png</companylogo>
			</job>
	<job>
		<title>Retail Team Leader</title>
		<date>2024-01-03T14:05:50.000000Z</date>
		<expirationdate>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000000Z</expirationdate>
		<referencenumber>2806</referencenumber>
		<url>https://midlandjobs.ie/job/2806/retail-team-leader/</url>
		<city>Ballymahon</city>
		<state>County Longford</state>
		<country>Ireland</country>
		<postalcode></postalcode>
		<location></location>
		<remote>no</remote>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re a thriving team passionate about working together to deliver excellence, all in a natural forest environment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in hundreds of acres of beautiful forest Longford Forest is the perfect place for a short break in Ireland, 365 days a year. With homely accommodation, up to 100 indoor and outdoor activities and a choice of bars and restaurants, there is something for all the family, all year round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RETAIL TEAM LEADER | €15.19 per hour&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On a Center Parcs break we want our guests to relax knowing everything is taken care of. Our Retail department provides a fantastic shopping experience, from essential groceries to luxury items. Across the village there are a number of retail units, both own brand and concession units.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for motivated, outgoing and service-orientated individuals to join the retail team as a Team Leader.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your role will be to assist with managing a team of colleagues in order to deliver budgeted financial targets, service targets and operational standards, whilst ensuring our guests’ experience is memorable and unique. You should display a positive image in both appearance &amp;amp; gesture, be able to listen to our guests and take ownership of queries or issues. In addition, you will need to take duty management responsibility of the Center Parcs owned retail outlets on a defined shift basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT YOU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous Supervisory experience in a Retail or similar guest facing role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To be able to demonstrate the ability to communicate effectively at all levels, and coach others to deliver objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desirable requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of retail merchandising gained in a food environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competence of MS Office programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of retail EPOS (Electronic Point of Sale)/Stock control systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOURS OF WORK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be contracted to work 150 hours per 4-week period on a flexible basis, this means your days and hours of work could vary each week but you will always receive your contracted hours each period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your working hours will include a range of shifts, including; mornings, evenings, weekends, public / bank holidays and during Christmas and/or New Year on a rota basis, with a premium rate of pay for hours worked on a Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE BENEFITS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Center Parcs is a fantastic place to work and the benefits are as impressive as they are unique. Here are just a few:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Bonus Scheme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pension Scheme with Life Assurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Recognition and Reward Scheme – offering a choice of Center Parcs and High Street vouchers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free use of our leisure facilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discounted Center Parcs breaks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20% discount in our restaurant and retail outlets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to Perks at Work Portal - offering a wide range of retail and leisure discounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Employee Assistance Program - providing support on financial, health and legal matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excellent opportunities for career development and progression with the opportunity to gain externally recognised qualifications&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like your ideal job, then we’d love to see your application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
					<salary>€15.19 hourly</salary>
			<salaryfrom>15.19</salaryfrom>
			<salaryto>15.19</salaryto>
			<salaryperiod>hourly</salaryperiod>
				<applyurl>https://bit.ly/3RKeDr7</applyurl>
		<jobtype>Full time</jobtype>
		<category>Retail</category>
		<company>Center Parcs Ltd</company>
		<companydescription>&lt;p&gt;Imagine being greeted by playful squirrels and a good morning &amp;lsquo;quack!&amp;rsquo; by the local ducks on your commute into work. Imagine having a workplace that&amp;rsquo;s up to 400 acres of beautiful forest. Imagine being part of a family where you love coming to work and helping to make special memories. At Center Parcs, you can have all that and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Housekeeper, Chef, Lifeguard or Electrician, everyone is part of the same Center Parcs family, and no two days are the same. If you are looking for a unique place to work with endless opportunities and famously good staff perks, visit our vacancies page and apply to work at Center Parcs.&lt;/p&gt;</companydescription>
		<companywebsite>https://www.centerparcs.ie/</companywebsite>
		<companylogo>https://midlandjobs.ie/files/pictures/CP_Logo_MASTER_IRELAND_1042x1042_png.png</companylogo>
			</job>
	<job>
		<title>Housekeeper / Cleaner - Accommodation</title>
		<date>2024-01-03T14:03:40.000000Z</date>
		<expirationdate>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000000Z</expirationdate>
		<referencenumber>2804</referencenumber>
		<url>https://midlandjobs.ie/job/2804/housekeeper-cleaner-accommodation/</url>
		<city>Ballymahon</city>
		<state>County Longford</state>
		<country>Ireland</country>
		<postalcode></postalcode>
		<location></location>
		<remote>no</remote>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re a thriving team passionate about working together to deliver excellence, all in a natural forest environment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in hundreds of acres of beautiful forest Longford Forest is the perfect place for a short break in Ireland, 365 days a year. With homely accommodation, up to 100 indoor and outdoor activities and a choice of bars and restaurants, there is something for all the family, all year round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOUSEKEEPER / CLEANER - ACCOMMODATION | €12.90 per hour&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This role involves carrying out cleaning duties in 3 / 4 units of accommodation, including; stripping and making beds, cleaning bathrooms and kitchens, dusting, vacuuming, and sweeping patios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOURS OF WORK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a part-time role, working Mondays and Fridays only from 10:00am to 2:45pm and we can offer you &lt;strong&gt;free transport&lt;/strong&gt; to and from work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT YOU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t need any experience in cleaning as full training will be provided and you will be surrounded by a supportive team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can bring the following qualities and skills then we’d love to hear from you:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills – confident to talk to guests and your colleagues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An awareness of general standards of cleanliness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT THE BENEFITS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Center Parcs is a fantastic place to work and the benefits are as impressive as they are unique. Here are just a few:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Day passes for you and your family / friends to access the village&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free use of our leisure facilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discounted Center Parcs breaks – up to 60% off a short break with us&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20% discount in our restaurants and retail outlets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Bonus Scheme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pension Scheme with Life Assurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Recognition and Reward Scheme – offering a choice of Center Parcs and High Street vouchers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to Perks at Work Portal - offering a wide range of retail and leisure discounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Employee Assistance Program - providing support on financial, health and legal matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent opportunities for career development and progression with the opportunity to gain externally recognised qualifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If joining our Housekeeping team sounds like your ideal job, then we’d love to see your application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Initial contact will be made via telephone and then interviews will be carried out following social distancing measures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
					<salary>€12.90 hourly</salary>
			<salaryfrom>12.90</salaryfrom>
			<salaryto>12.90</salaryto>
			<salaryperiod>hourly</salaryperiod>
				<applyurl>https://bit.ly/3tzJuyH</applyurl>
		<jobtype>Part time</jobtype>
		<category>Hospitality-Hotel</category>
		<company>Center Parcs Ltd</company>
		<companydescription>&lt;p&gt;Imagine being greeted by playful squirrels and a good morning &amp;lsquo;quack!&amp;rsquo; by the local ducks on your commute into work. Imagine having a workplace that&amp;rsquo;s up to 400 acres of beautiful forest. Imagine being part of a family where you love coming to work and helping to make special memories. At Center Parcs, you can have all that and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Housekeeper, Chef, Lifeguard or Electrician, everyone is part of the same Center Parcs family, and no two days are the same. If you are looking for a unique place to work with endless opportunities and famously good staff perks, visit our vacancies page and apply to work at Center Parcs.&lt;/p&gt;</companydescription>
		<companywebsite>https://www.centerparcs.ie/</companywebsite>
		<companylogo>https://midlandjobs.ie/files/pictures/CP_Logo_MASTER_IRELAND_1042x1042_png.png</companylogo>
			</job>
	<job>
		<title>Bar and Waiting Team Member</title>
		<date>2024-01-03T13:58:39.000000Z</date>
		<expirationdate>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000000Z</expirationdate>
		<referencenumber>2802</referencenumber>
		<url>https://midlandjobs.ie/job/2802/bar-and-waiting-team-member/</url>
		<city>Ballymahon</city>
		<state>County Longford</state>
		<country>Ireland</country>
		<postalcode></postalcode>
		<location></location>
		<remote>no</remote>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re a thriving team passionate about working together to deliver excellence, all in a natural forest environment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in hundreds of acres of beautiful forest Longford Forest is the perfect place for a short break in Ireland, 365 days a year. With homely accommodation, up to 100 indoor and outdoor activities and a choice of bars and restaurants, there is something for all the family, all year round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BAR AND WAITING TEAM MEMBER | €12.90 Per Hour&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;All colleagues working in our restaurants, cafés and bars will benefit from the discretionary service charge we add to bills. The majority of our guests are happy to reward our colleagues for their excellent service.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Longford Forest, the Food and Beverage department employs around 300 team members across 10 different restaurants, cafés and bars, as well as a production kitchen. From Italian and American grills to Indian and Asian Fusion cuisine, or for those wanting a relaxing drink after a busy day, there’s something to suit all appetites at Center Parcs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Centre stage and front of house, our Bar and Waiting team members are at the heart of village life, continually meeting and exceeding the expectations of our guests…day after day and we are now looking for a large team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your day to day duties will include welcoming and seating guests, taking orders, bar service, serving food and drinks and maintaining a clean working environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will have a passion for delivering excellent customer service, have great communication skills and enjoy working as part of a team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT YOU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whilst previous hospitality or customer service experience would be an advantage, full training will be provided for these roles so all that we ask is that you are a cheerful, friendly and approachable individual who will enjoy speaking with our guests and working with an amazing team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOURS OF WORK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be contracted to work 150 hours per 4-week period on a flexible basis, this means your days and hours of work could vary each week but you will always receive your contracted hours each period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your working hours will include a range of shifts, including; mornings, evenings, weekends, public / bank holidays and during Christmas and/or New Year on a rota basis, with a premium rate of pay for hours worked on a Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE BENEFITS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Center Parcs is a fantastic place to work and the benefits are as impressive as they are unique. Here are just a few:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Bonus Scheme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pension Scheme with Life Assurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Recognition and Reward Scheme – offering a choice of Center Parcs and High Street vouchers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free use of our leisure facilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discounted Center Parcs breaks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20% discount in our restaurant and retail outlets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Employee Assistance Program - providing support on financial, health and legal matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent opportunities for career development and progression with the opportunity to gain externally recognised qualifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like your ideal job, then we’d love to see your application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
					<salary>€12.90 hourly</salary>
			<salaryfrom>12.90</salaryfrom>
			<salaryto>12.90</salaryto>
			<salaryperiod>hourly</salaryperiod>
				<applyurl>https://bit.ly/41GECo0</applyurl>
		<jobtype>Full time</jobtype>
		<category>Restaurant-Food Service</category>
		<company>Center Parcs Ltd</company>
		<companydescription>&lt;p&gt;Imagine being greeted by playful squirrels and a good morning &amp;lsquo;quack!&amp;rsquo; by the local ducks on your commute into work. Imagine having a workplace that&amp;rsquo;s up to 400 acres of beautiful forest. Imagine being part of a family where you love coming to work and helping to make special memories. At Center Parcs, you can have all that and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Housekeeper, Chef, Lifeguard or Electrician, everyone is part of the same Center Parcs family, and no two days are the same. If you are looking for a unique place to work with endless opportunities and famously good staff perks, visit our vacancies page and apply to work at Center Parcs.&lt;/p&gt;</companydescription>
		<companywebsite>https://www.centerparcs.ie/</companywebsite>
		<companylogo>https://midlandjobs.ie/files/pictures/CP_Logo_MASTER_IRELAND_1042x1042_png.png</companylogo>
			</job>
	<job>
		<title>Linen and Logistics Assistant Team Leader / Supervisor</title>
		<date>2024-01-03T13:50:36.000000Z</date>
		<expirationdate>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000000Z</expirationdate>
		<referencenumber>2799</referencenumber>
		<url>https://midlandjobs.ie/job/2799/linen-and-logistics-assistant-team-leader-supervisor/</url>
		<city>Ballymahon</city>
		<state>County Longford</state>
		<country>Ireland</country>
		<postalcode></postalcode>
		<location></location>
		<remote>no</remote>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re a thriving team passionate about working together to deliver excellence, all in a natural forest environment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in hundreds of acres of beautiful forest Longford Forest is the perfect place for a short break in Ireland, 365 days a year. With homely accommodation, up to 100 indoor and outdoor activities and a choice of bars and restaurants, there is something for all the family, all year round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT THE ROLE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LINEN AND LOGISTICS ASSISTANT TEAM LEADER / SUPERVISOR | €13.58 per hour&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Linen Assistant Team Leader, you will be responsible for a team of up to 3 Linen Assistants. Your main duties will include the co-ordination and delivery of all linen items within your team as well as the safe loading and unloading of linen vehicles. You must ensure your team deliver supplies to all accommodation units within your area in a timely and efficient manner. You may also be required to order and deliver additional inventory items and sundries to guest accommodation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your role also requires you to support the training and development needs of your team members and regularly report to the Head of Department.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The role will be very ‘hands on’, leading from the front, working with your team to ensure all guests receive an amazing Center Parcs experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT YOU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good verbal and written communication skills are required, along with an organised and methodical approach to work.  The ideal candidate will be flexible and adaptable, have a motivational approach and have previous supervisory experience. Previous experience within the cleaning / hospitality industry would be preferred but not essential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full Driving Licence held for a minimum of 6 months&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills, both verbal and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desirable requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous supervisory experience within the cleaning industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOURS OF WORK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be contracted to work either 62 or 42 hours per 4-week period on a flexible basis, which means your days and hours of work could vary each week but you will always receive your contracted hours each period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will also be required to work weekends and public/bank holidays on a rota basis with a premium rate of pay for hours worked on a Sunday. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE BENEFITS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Center Parcs is a fantastic place to work and the benefits are as impressive as they are unique. Here are just a few:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Bonus Scheme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pension Scheme with Life Assurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Recognition and Reward Scheme – offering a choice of Center Parcs and High Street vouchers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free use of our leisure facilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discounted Center Parcs breaks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20% discount in our restaurant and retail outlets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to Perks at Work Portal - offering a wide range of retail and leisure discounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Employee Assistance Program - providing support on financial, health and legal matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent opportunities for career development and progression with the opportunity to gain externally recognised qualifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like your ideal job, then we’d love to see your application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
					<salary>€13.58 hourly</salary>
			<salaryfrom>13.58</salaryfrom>
			<salaryto>13.58</salaryto>
			<salaryperiod>hourly</salaryperiod>
				<applyurl>https://bit.ly/48EVs8U</applyurl>
		<jobtype>Part time</jobtype>
		<category>Hospitality-Hotel</category>
		<company>Center Parcs Ltd</company>
		<companydescription>&lt;p&gt;Imagine being greeted by playful squirrels and a good morning &amp;lsquo;quack!&amp;rsquo; by the local ducks on your commute into work. Imagine having a workplace that&amp;rsquo;s up to 400 acres of beautiful forest. Imagine being part of a family where you love coming to work and helping to make special memories. At Center Parcs, you can have all that and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Housekeeper, Chef, Lifeguard or Electrician, everyone is part of the same Center Parcs family, and no two days are the same. If you are looking for a unique place to work with endless opportunities and famously good staff perks, visit our vacancies page and apply to work at Center Parcs.&lt;/p&gt;</companydescription>
		<companywebsite>https://www.centerparcs.ie/</companywebsite>
		<companylogo>https://midlandjobs.ie/files/pictures/CP_Logo_MASTER_IRELAND_1042x1042_png.png</companylogo>
			</job>
	<job>
		<title>Spa Beauty Therapist</title>
		<date>2024-01-03T13:45:04.000000Z</date>
		<expirationdate>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000000Z</expirationdate>
		<referencenumber>2795</referencenumber>
		<url>https://midlandjobs.ie/job/2795/spa-beauty-therapist/</url>
		<city>Ballymahon</city>
		<state>County Longford</state>
		<country>Ireland</country>
		<postalcode></postalcode>
		<location></location>
		<remote>no</remote>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Aqua Sana is a unique, multi-award-winning spa in the heart of the forest, with six locations across the UK and Ireland. Recent awards include ‘Best Destination Spa’, ‘Best Day Spa’ and ‘National Spa of the Year’.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPA BEAUTY THERAPIST | €15.07 per hour plus commission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discover extraordinary benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy heavily discounted Center Parcs breaks, free use of our spa facilities, opportunities to earn retail commission, free day passes for you and your family, and discounts in our restaurants and retail outlets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stay up to date with new trends and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We offer in-house training on beauty brand treatments, along with wellness and holistic therapies. We even create our own treatments, drawing upon the experience and skills of our Therapist family.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Career progression opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alongside our in-house training and development of new skills, you will also have the opportunity to gain externally recognised qualifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A unique working environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our tranquil spa is tucked away in the heart of the forest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work with like-minded people&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A friendly and welcoming team who are passionate about wellbeing and beauty, and keen to share their knowledge and skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aqua Sana Spa is proud to work with some of the most luxurious skincare brands available on the market, namely Elemis and VOYA. From massages to manicures, facials to full body treatments, you’ll love providing our range of holistic, therapeutic, express and beauty treatments. You will also assist our guests to select the perfect items from our comprehensive retail offering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have six spa locations across UK and Ireland. Each one offers something a little different, with different spa experiences, layouts and surroundings, but one thing they have in common is the people. Making our guests feel amazing is at the heart of what we do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you step through our doors, we want you to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a desire to deliver consistently high standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to prepare well and keep to a timetable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be naturally cheerful, friendly and approachable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have excellent communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 6 Beauty Therapy or equivalent qualification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Level 3 Diploma in Body Massage or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desirable requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reflexology qualification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience working within a salon or spa environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product training on Elemis, OPI, Mii Makeup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Due to the sensitive nature of this role the successful applicant will be required to apply for Garda Vetting. This disclosure, together with other selection information, will need to be satisfactory to the Company for employment to commence.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOURS OF WORK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have various full and part-time contracts available, with shifts falling between 9:30am and 10:00pm, including some weekends. For full-time roles you will only be required to work 2 out of 4 weekends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As our village is open 365 days of the year, your working hours will include weekends, public / bank holidays and during Christmas and / or New Year on a rota basis, with a premium rate of pay for hours worked on a Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REWARDS AND BENEFITS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your training at Aqua Sana Spa doesn’t stop with your induction; it’s only the beginning. We offer regular in-house training courses so you can keep ahead of new treatments and wellness trends, and your individual development will be supported every step of the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Health and wellbeing are central to our ethos, so we actively encourage our staff to use the spa facilities free of charge because a relaxed and happy team are an amazing asset for us and our guests. And as the work can be quite physical, we restrict massage to 4.5 hours a day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As well as a free uniform, your retail commission, huge discounts off breaks at Center Parcs, discounts in our retail outlets and restaurants and free day passes for you and your friends or family, our other benefits include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Bonus Scheme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleague Recognition and Reward Scheme – offering a choice of Center Parcs and High Street vouchers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to Perks at Work Portal - offering a wide range of retail and leisure discounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Employee Assistance Program - providing support on financial, health and legal matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pension Scheme with Life Assurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent opportunities for career development and progression with the opportunity to gain externally recognised qualifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like your ideal job, then we’d love to see your application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
					<salary>€15.07 hourly</salary>
			<salaryfrom>15.07</salaryfrom>
			<salaryto>15.07</salaryto>
			<salaryperiod>hourly</salaryperiod>
				<applyurl>https://bit.ly/3TKeGFS</applyurl>
		<jobtype>Full time</jobtype>
		<category>Beauty / Hairdressing</category>
		<company>Center Parcs Ltd</company>
		<companydescription>&lt;p&gt;Imagine being greeted by playful squirrels and a good morning &amp;lsquo;quack!&amp;rsquo; by the local ducks on your commute into work. Imagine having a workplace that&amp;rsquo;s up to 400 acres of beautiful forest. Imagine being part of a family where you love coming to work and helping to make special memories. At Center Parcs, you can have all that and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Housekeeper, Chef, Lifeguard or Electrician, everyone is part of the same Center Parcs family, and no two days are the same. If you are looking for a unique place to work with endless opportunities and famously good staff perks, visit our vacancies page and apply to work at Center Parcs.&lt;/p&gt;</companydescription>
		<companywebsite>https://www.centerparcs.ie/</companywebsite>
		<companylogo>https://midlandjobs.ie/files/pictures/CP_Logo_MASTER_IRELAND_1042x1042_png.png</companylogo>
			</job>
</source>